Welcome to today's tutorial, where we'll be learning the basics of iterating
歡迎來到今天的課程，我們會在這裡學習到基本的迭代
through a CSV file to create dictionaries and collect summary statistics.
通過一個.csv文件，來創建字典和收集匯總統計。
First, let's import the CSV module, which will assist us in reading in our CSV file.
首先，讓我們導入.csv程序模組，它將幫助我們去讀進我們的.csv文件。
Using some iPython magic,
使用一些Python魔法，
let's set the floating point precision for printing to 2.
讓我們設置列印的浮點數據精度為2。
Now let's read in our mpg.csv using csv.DictReader and
現在讓我們使用csv.DictReader讀取我們的mpg.csv
convert it to a list of dictionaries.
並將其轉換為列表的字典。
Let's look at the first three elements of our list.
我們來看看我們列表中的前三個元素。
We can see that the dictionaries in the list have the column names of the CSV as
我們可以看到列表中的字典具有.csv的列欄名稱
keys, and data for each specific car are the values.
作為keys，和每個特定車的數據都是它的values。
The length of our list is 234,
我們的列表的長度是234，
meaning we have a dictionary for each of the 234 cars in the CSV file.
這意味著我們有234個汽車的字典在.csv文件中。
We can look at what the column names of the CSV are by using the key method.
我們可以查看.csv列欄名稱，使用key的方法。
Suppose we want to find the average city MPG across all cars in our CSV file.
假設我們要找到所有車輛的平均城市mpg，從我們的.csv文件。
We sum the city MPG entry across all the dictionaries in our list and
我們總計列表中的所有字典的城市mpg資料，
divide by the length of the list.
並除以列表的長度。
Because the type for all the values in our dictionary are strings,
因為我們的字典中所有的值的類型都是strings，
we need to convert to float to perform mathematical operations.
所以我們需要轉換為float來執行數學運算。
Similarly, we can find the average highway MPG across all the cars in our CSV file.
同樣的，我們可以在我們的.csv文件中找到所有汽車的平均公路mpg。
And it makes sense that the average highway fuel economy is higher than in
平均公路燃油經濟性高於
the city.
城市是合理的。
Now, let's look at a more complex example.
現在，讓我們看看一個更複雜的例子。
Say we want to know what the average city MPG is
比如說我們想要知道平均城市mpg是什麼，
grouped by the number of cylinders a car has.
但按照一輛車的汽缸數目來分組。
Creating a set of the values in the cylinder entry of the dictionaries
從字典的汽缸資料創建一組數值，
will give us the unique levels for a number of cylinders.
會給我們的獨特的汽缸數目。
We see that we have cars in out dataset with 4, 5, 6, and 8 cylinders.
我們看到我們車的資料有4、5、6和8個汽缸。
First, we'll create an empty list where we'll store our calculations.
首先，我們將創建一個空的list，我們將在其中存儲我們的計算。
Next, let's iterate over all the cylinder levels.
接下來，讓我們迭代所有的汽缸數目。
And then we'll iterate over all the dictionaries.
然後我們將反覆迭代所有的字典。
If the cylinder level for the dictionary we're on
如果我們在字典的汽缸數目級別，
matches the cylinder level we're calculating the average for,
符合我們要計算的平均水準的汽缸數目級別，
we add the mpg to our summpg variable and increment the count.
我們加mpg數值到我們的summpg變數和遞增計數。
After going through all the dictionaries, we perform the average MPG calculation and
經過所有的字典資料，我們計算平均mpg和
append it to our list.
將它添加到我們的列表中。
To make things clearer,
為了讓事情更清楚，
I'm going to sort the list from lowest number of cylinders to highest.
我將列表從最低數目的汽缸排列到最高的。
And we can see that the city fuel economy appears to be decreasing as the number of
我們可以看到城市燃油經濟性似乎在下降，隨著
cylinders increases.
汽缸的數目增加。
Let's look at one more similar example.
讓我們看多一個類似的例子。
Suppose we're interested in finding the average highway MPG for
假設我們有興趣尋找平均公路mpg
the different vehicle classes.
在不同的車輛類別中。
Looking at the different vehicle classes, we have 2seater, compact, midsize,
從不同車輛類別來看，我們有2座車、小型車、中型車，
minivan, pickup, subcompact, and SUV.
迷你麵包車、小貨車、微型車和運動型多用途車SUV。
Similar to the last example, we iterate over all the vehicle classes,
同樣與上一個例子，我們遍歷所有類別的車輛，
then iterate over all the dictionaries.
然後我們將反覆迭代所有的字典。
If the vehicle class for
如果車輛類別
the dictionary matches the vehicle class we're computing the average
在字典裡與我們正在計算平均公路mpg的車輛類別相符合
highway MPG for, we add the value to our total, and increment the count.
，我們將值添加到我們的總數，並遞增計數。
Then we perform the average calculation and append it to our list.
然後我們進行平均計算，並將其追加到我們的清單中。
This time, let's sort our list from lowest MPG to highest.
這次，讓我們列表從最低mpg到最高的進行排序。
Looks like the pickup had the worst fuel economy and the compact had the best.
看起來像小貨車有最糟糕的燃油經濟性，小型車的最好。
So that was a look into how to summarize data through iteration.
這就是通過迭代來總結數據的方法。
Don't worry if this seems somewhat inefficient or tedious.
不要擔心，如果這似乎有點低效或乏味。
Next week, we will be learning about Pandas, a Python library that allows for
下個星期，我們將會學習Pandas，一個Python程序模組，可以在Python中
easier, more efficient, and more powerful data analysis in Python.
實現更簡單，更高效，更強大的數據分析。
Thanks for watching.
感謝收看！
Hope to see you again soon.
感謝您的收看。希望能很快見到你。